techlogon.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy | TechLogon Technology News

**Privacy Policy for Techlogon.com**

The privacy of visitors to Techlogon.com is important to us.

Listed below are details of what types of personal information we receive and/or collect when you use or visit Techlogon.com and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Cookies / Web Beacons / Advertising**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you an advert once in your visit or the ability to access some of the website features.

We also use third party advertisements on Techlogon.com to support the site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and/or web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Adobe Flash Player installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York airport adverts to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain adverts based on specific sites you have visited (e.g. showing music adverts to someone who frequents music sites).

Techlogon is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com and/or other international amazon sites.

 **DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We may also use DART cookies for advert serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve adverts specific to you and your interests (i.e. ‘interest based targeting’). The adverts served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Washington, you may see Washington hotel adverts when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about baseball).

DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone numbers, passwords, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt out of this interest based advert serving by visiting <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads>

You can also opt out of the interest based advert serving of many third party advert servers and networks simultaneously by visiting[ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Opting out of a network does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver adverts tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns.

You can also choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your web browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opting out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the adverts, a new cookie will be added.

 **Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we may collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files may include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider, such as AOL), the web browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
